Guide to the Frank Clyde Brown papers, 1912-1974 RL.00160
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Cylinders and Discs, 10 boxes
  - Phonodiscs, 1936-1941
    - RL00160-PD-0045_02, 1940-08-08 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0045_02)
      Title: Georgie, performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:57:768
    - RL00160-PD-0046_01, 1940-08-08 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0046_01)
      Title: Our Goodman (My Goodman), performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:21:609
      Title: Granny Frome's Witch Tale [Prose], performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:06:30:754
      Title: Jealous Lover, performer: Hart, Lona, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:38:398
    - RL00160-PD-0046_02, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0046_02)
      Title: Lord Lovel, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:31:436
      Title: [Blank], performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:30:900
      Title: FCB talking, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:39:356
      Title: Barbara Allen, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:36:093
      Title: Barbara Allen, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:30:511
      Title: unknown, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:25:997
      Title: Drink To Me Only With Thy Eyes, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:35:136
    - RL00160-PD-0047_01, 1940-08-13 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0047_01)
      Title: The Twelve Apotles (Come I Will Sing You), performer: Walker, Edith, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:05:04:882
      Title: The Knocking On the Barrel [Prose tale], performer: Wood, Granny', location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:58:352
      Title: Ghost Story - Personal Experience [Prose tale], performer: Thomas, Ettie, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:42:328
    - RL00160-PD-0047_02, 1940-08-13 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0047_02)
      Title: Three Witch Tales [Prose], performer: Thomas, Ettie, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:51:840
      Title: Seeing the Coffin [Witch tale], performer: Thomas, Ettie, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:23:769
      Title: The Four-Horse Wagon [Prose tale], performer: Thomas, Ettie, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:09:426
      Title: A Treasure Hunt [Prose tale], performer: Thomas, Ettie, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:21:500
      Title: Witch a Gossip [Prose tale], performer: Thomas, Ettie, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:10:270
    - RL00160-PD-0048_01, 1940-08-28 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0048_01)
      Title: Young Beichan (Susan Price), performer: Hicks, Nora | Hicks, Addie, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:42:082
      Title: Young Charlotte, performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:26:421
      Title: Lady Isabel and the Elf Knight, performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:22:503
    - RL00160-PD-0048_02, 1940-08-28 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0048_02)
      Title: Lady Isabel and the Elf Knight (cont), performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:02:441
      Title: Pretty Polly, performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:47:743
      Title: Fair Margaret and Sweet William (Lady Margaret), performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:47:456
    - RL00160-PD-0049_01, 1940-08-28 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0049_01)
      Title: William Riley, performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:26:299
      Title: Sweet Sailor Boy, performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:28:784
      Title: George Collins, performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:33:187
      Title: James Harris (House Carpenter), performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:38:160
    - RL00160-PD-0049_02, 1940-08-28 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0049_02)
      Title: Lord Thomas and Fair Annet (Lord Thomas andFair Annet Ellinger), performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:44:596
      Title: The Sweet Trinity (Golden Willow Tree), performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:03:319
      Title: William Riley, performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:03:019
    - RL00160-PD-0050_01, 1940-09-04 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0050_01)
      Title: Lord Randall (Jimmy Randall) (Polly Von), performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:42:031
      Title: The Rich Lady From London, performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:15:191
      Title: The Lineback Hant [Prose tale], performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Hughes (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:05:065
    - RL00160-PD-0050_02, 1940-09-04 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0050_02)
      Title: The Lineback Hant [Prose tale - concluded], performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Hughes (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:10:04:615
    - RL00160-PD-0051_01, 1940-09-30 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0051_01)
      Title: Little Musgrove and Lady Barnard (Lord Daniel's Wife), performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:18:615
      Title: Little Musgrove and Lady Barnard (Lord Daniel's Wife), performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:21:719
      Title: Gypsie Laddie (Black Jack Davy), performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:43:056
      Title: Lord Lovel, performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:10:009
    - RL00160-PD-0051_02, 1940-09-30 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0051_02)
      Title: Jimmy Caldwell, performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:33:549
      Title: The Wife of Usher's Well (Lady Bright), performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:46:807
      Title: Robin Hood and the Beggar, performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:04:990
      Title: Robin Hood and the Beggar, performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:12:780
    - RL00160-PD-0052_01, 1940-09-05 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0052_01)
      Title: The Drunkard's Confession, performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:27:823
      Title: Crucified Jesus, performer: Hicks, Nora, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:00:609
      Title: unknown, performer: unknown, location: Mast Gap (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:11:479
    - RL00160-PD-0052_02, 1940-09-05 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0052_02)
      Title: Lord Randall, performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:36:706
      Title: Maid Freed From the Gallows (Hangman's Tree), performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:23:011
      Title: I Don't Know Why I Love Her, performer: Vance, Marylin | Binfield, Evelyn, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:03:280
    - RL00160-PD-0053_01, 1941-06-12 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0053_01)
      Title: When the Saints Go Marching In, performer: Alice the cook, location: Greensboro (N.C.) | Guilford County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:10:038
    - RL00160-PD-0054_01, 1941-09-14 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0054_01)
      Title: Child Riddles, performer: Weavers Bonny, The, location: Virginia, running time: 00:00:56:954
      Title: The Two Sisters (Old Man from North Countree), performer: Weavers Bonny, The, location: Virginia, running time: 00:00:40:639
      Title: There Was an Old Woman In Our Town, performer: Weavers Bonny, The, location: Virginia, running time: 00:00:43:745
      Title: The Brown Girl (Sweet Sally), performer: Weavers Bonny, The, location: Virginia, running time: 00:01:06:914
      Title: Edward, performer: Weavers Bonny, The, location: Virginia, running time: 00:03:04:253
    - RL00160-PD-0054_02, 1941-09-14 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0054_02)
      Title: The Maid Freed From the Gallows (Hangman, Hangman), performer: Church, Steve, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:12:272
      Title: The Maid Freed From the Gallows (Hangman, Hangman), performer: Johnson, Anna, location: North Wilkesboro (N.C.) | Wilkes County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:44:000
      Title: Lord Thomas and Fair Annet, performer: Barker, Horton, location: unknown, running time: 00:02:17:253
      Title: The Riddle Song, performer: Barker, Horton, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:28:779
      Title: Claud Allen, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:23:099
      Title: Fair Margaret and Sweet William, performer: York, James, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:20:139
      Title: The Cambrie Shirt, performer: York, James, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:09:667
    - RL00160-PD-0055_01, 1939 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0055_01)
      Title: Jack's Gone A-Calling, performer: York, James, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:33:358
      Title: The Two Sisters, performer: Johnson, Anna, location: North Wilkesboro (N.C.) | Wilkes County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:07:232
      Title: Karl Brand, performer: Johnson, Anna, location: North Wilkesboro (N.C.) | Wilkes County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:55:027
      Title: Early, Early In the Spring, performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:54:396
      Title: James Harris (The House Carpenter), performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:25:980
    - RL00160-PD-0055_02, 1941-09-14 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0055_02)
      Title: The Sweet Trinity (The Golden Willow Tree), performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:46:103
      Title: Young Johnny, performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:20:407
      Title: Get Up and Bar the Door, performer: York, James, location: Olin (N.C.) | Iredell County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:02:920
    - RL00160-PD-0056_01, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0056_01)
      Title: July 14th 1939 in Blowing Rock..., performer: unknown, location: Blowing Rock (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.) | Caldwell County (N.C.), running time:
      Title: George Collins, performer: unknown, location: Blowing Rock (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.) | Caldwell County (N.C.), running time:
      Title: Talking, performer: unknown, location: Blowing Rock (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.) | Caldwell County (N.C.), running time:
      Title: Lord Lovel, performer: unknown, location: Blowing Rock (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.) | Caldwell County (N.C.), running time:
    - RL00160-PD-0056_02, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0056_02)
      Title: Lord Lovel (and Lady Nancy), performer: unknown, location: Blowing Rock (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.) | Caldwell County (N.C.), running time:
      Title: Will You Love Me In December As You Do In May, performer: unknown, location: Blowing Rock (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.) | Caldwell County (N.C.), running time:
      Title: Poem 1, performer: unknown, location: Blowing Rock (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.) | Caldwell County (N.C.), running time:
    - RL00160-PD-0057_01, 1936-07-21 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0057_01)
      Title: Floyd Collins, performer: Barker, Horton, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:31:210
      Title: Kind Wife, performer: Barker, Horton, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:30:104
    - RL00160-PD-0057_02, 1936-06-02 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0057_02)
      Title: Barbara Allen, performer: Tarwater, Becky, location: Redwood (TN) | Tennessee, running time: 00:02:34:280
    - RL00160-PD-0058_01, 1936-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0058_01)
      Title: Monday I Was Arrested, performer: unknown, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:37:976
      Title: Pick em Up (Lulu), performer: unknown, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:31:700
    - RL00160-PD-0058_02, 1936-07-18 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0058_02)
      Title: Remember Me, performer: unknown, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:31:967
      Title: Blues: You Have Me Down, Babe [solo], performer: unknown, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:16:194
    - RL00160-PD-0059_01, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0059_01)
      Title: Songs of the Buffaloe, performer: Lomax, John A., location: unknown, running time: 00:01:41:483
    - RL00160-PD-0059_02, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0059_02)
      Title: Seven Year Song, performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:25:289
    - RL00160-PD-0060_01, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0060_01)
      Title: The Knoxville Girl (The Lexington Murder), performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:02:09:557
      Title: On a Dark and Stormy night, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:36:833
      Title: Away on a Hill, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:31:416
    - RL00160-PD-0060_02, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0060_02)
      Title: Ground Hog, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:00:076
    - RL00160-PD-0061_01, 1936-07-22 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0061_01)
      Title: Seven Years Song (Pretty Fair Maid), performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:33:861
      Title: Young Johnny, performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:50:023
    - RL00160-PD-0061_02, 1936-07-22 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0061_02)
      Title: The Sweet Trinity (Golden Willow Tree), performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:38:699
      Title: Lass of Loch Royal, performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:57:501
    - RL00160-PD-0062_01, 1936-07-22 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0062_01)
      Title: Wagonner's Lad, performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:02:291
      Title: Wagonner's Lad, performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:03:979
      Title: Sweet Willie, performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:33:071
    - RL00160-PD-0062_02, 1936-07-22 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0062_02)
      Title: James Harris (House Carpenter), performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:34:156
    - RL00160-PD-0063_01, 1936-07-22 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0063_01)
      Title: Our Good Man (Good Wife, Kind Wife), performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:28:034
      Title: Lord Lovel, performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:55:307
      Title: unknown, performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:14:608
      Title: Romish Lady, performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:32:128
      Title: Brown Girl, performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:16:448
    - RL00160-PD-0063_02, 1936-07-22 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0063_02)
      Title: Brown Girl (continued), performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:30:420
      Title: When Young Men Go A-Courting, performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:58:749
    - RL00160-PD-0064_01, 1936-07-22 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0064_01)
      Title: Lady Isabel and the Elf Knight (Six Fair Maids), performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:09:821
    - RL00160-PD-0064_02, 1936-07-22 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0064_02)
      Title: James Harris (The House Carpenter), performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:05:10:839
    - RL00160-PD-0065_01, 1936-07 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0065_01)
      Title: GroundHog, performer: Wright, J.T.C., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:54:505
      Title: Barbara Allen, performer: Beaker, H.J., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:15:637
    - RL00160-PD-0065_02, 1936-07 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0065_02)
      Title: Burglar Man, performer: Beaker, H.J., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:54:219
      Title: Don't Let the Girls Worry My Mind, performer: Beaker, H.J., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:51:082
      Title: Frankie and Johnny, performer: Beaker, H.J., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:32:299
    - RL00160-PD-0066_01, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0066_01)
      Title: One Morning in May, performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:01:259
    - RL00160-PD-0066_02, undated (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0066_02)
      Title: The Rambling Boy, performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:46:603
      Title: Hog Drovers, performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:49:071
      Title: Silk Merchant's Daughter, performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:06:086
      Title: Zion's Ship (Old Ship of Zion), performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: Tuckasegee (N.C.) | Jackson County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:50:425
      Title: Tom Dula, performer: Miller, Myra Barnett, location: unknown, running time: 00:01:05:209
    - RL00160-PD-0067_01, 1939-07-24 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0067_01)
      Title: Wife Wrapped Up In Weather's Skin (Dandoo), performer: Proffitt, Frank, location: Sugar Grove (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:28:578
      Title: Maid Freed From the Gallows (Hangman), performer: Proffitt, Frank, location: Sugar Grove (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:11:469
      Title: Rose Connally, performer: Proffitt, Frank, location: Sugar Grove (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:39:106
      Title: Barbara Allen, performer: Proffitt, Frank, location: Sugar Grove (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:03:429
    - RL00160-PD-0067_02, 1939-07-24 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0067_02)
      Title: George Collins, performer: Proffitt, Frank, location: Sugar Grove (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:23:029
      Title: Beau Lamkins [accompanied], performer: Proffitt, Frank, location: Sugar Grove (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:54:222
      Title: Beau Lamkins [unnaccompanied], performer: Proffitt, Frank, location: Sugar Grove (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:49:644
      Title: Gypsie Laddie (Black Jack Davy), performer: Proffitt, Frank, location: Sugar Grove (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:14:286
    - RL00160-PD-0068_01, 1939-07-26 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0068_01)
      Title: Our Goodman, performer: Proffitt, Frank, location: Sugar Grove (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:58:899
      Title: Pretty Polly (Wicked Polly), performer: Proffitt, Oliver, location: Sugar Grove (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:55:535
      Title: George Collins, performer: Hicks, Nora | Hicks, Nathan, location: Matney (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:29:890
    - RL00160-PD-0068_02, 1939-07-26 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0068_02)
      Title: Barbara Allen, performer: Hicks, Nora | Hicks, Nathan, location: Matney (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:04:12:443
    - RL00160-PD-0069_01, 1939-07-30 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0069_01)
      Title: Jack and the Man in the Chest, performer: Proffitt, Frank, location: Sugar Grove (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:03:16:099
      Title: Pretty Fair Maid, performer: Church, Y.F. (Grandpa), location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:54:355
      Title: I Once Loved a Young Man, performer: Trivette, John, location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:14:247
    - RL00160-PD-0069_02, 1939-07-30 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0069_02)
      Title: Advice to Young Ladies, performer: Trivette, John, location: Heaton (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:27:751
      Title: Lord Daniel's Wife, performer: Church, Jamie, location: Milam, running time: 00:02:23:512
    - RL00160-PD-0070_01, 1939-08-05 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0070_01)
      Title: Jennie Jenkins, performer: Prather, Nancy, location: Milam, running time: 00:01:46:169
      Title: Earl Brand, performer: Prather, Nancy, location: Milam, running time: 00:03:45:374
    - RL00160-PD-0070_02, 1939-08-05 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0070_02)
      Title: Lord Thomas and Fair Annet, performer: Prather, Nancy, location: Milam, running time: 00:03:23:864
      Title: Lord Randall, performer: Prather, Nancy, location: Milam, running time: 00:02:19:522
    - RL00160-PD-0071_01, 1939-08-05 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0071_01)
      Title: Little Musgrove and Lady Barnard (Little Matthy Groves), performer: Prather, Nancy, location: Milam, running time: 00:04:01:339
      Title: Lonely Tombs, performer: Oliver, Matthew | Lewis, Stella, location: Milam, running time: 00:01:44:842
    - RL00160-PD-0071_02, 1939-08-05 (Box 138, Audio-phonodisc RL00160-PD-0071_02)
      Title: Beaulamkin, performer: Prather, Nancy, location: Milam, running time: 00:04:05:758
      Title: Pretty Fair Maid, performer: Prather, Nancy, location: Milam, running time: 00:02:28:814